片名：終極戰士2
熱浪還在繼續 洛杉磯已高達109華氏度
The heat wave continues. it's 109 degrees in los angeles.
洛杉磯飽受乾旱之苦
As drought-ridden los angeles
高溫使人們備受折磨
swelters in agonising heat,...
而街頭的毒品稽查也在如火如荼的進行
..drug lords wage warfare in the streets.
又一次公開對抗還在...
Yet another open conflict...
天哪 快帶我離開這
oh, fuck this! get me out of here!
有兩名騎警在火拚中受重傷
Two motorcycle officers horribly wounded in a crossfire,...
警方似乎無力解救他們
The police seemingly unable to rescue them
多次英勇的突圍都沒有成功
in spite of several desperate,heroic attempts.
這裏已經完全失去控制
It's completely out of control down here.
我辛苦經營的酒吧全沒了
My beautiful cantina, everything I own,
什麼都被打碎了
they shot it to pieces.
我的微波爐 自動蒸鍋 烤箱
My microwave, my automatic steamer, my grill...
你們這群混蛋
You fucking pendejos!
去你們他媽的
Fuck you!
我是托尼·普波 這裏是核心現場節目
Tony pope, live with hard core
為您做現場報道
on the scene andin yourface.
這裏就像但丁描寫的地獄
It's like dante's hell.
硝煙 槍聲和難以忍受的高溫...
Smoke, fire, oppressive heat,...
哥倫比亞和牙買加的大煙鬼
As colombian and jamaican drug fiends
再次把洛杉磯變成了屠宰場
Again transform LA into a slaughterhouse.
這裏到底誰說了算 警察嗎 非也
Who the hell's in charge down here? the cops?Uh-uh
他們是人數眾多 裝備精良的笨蛋
They're outmanned, outgunned and incompetent.
在塔霍湖家中度假的市長先生
Mr mayor, on vacation in your home in lake tahoe,...
快把煙頭放下 趕快到這來頒布戒嚴令
..get off your butt, get down here and declare martial law!
別讓我心神不寧 丹尼
Ok, don't keep me in suspense, danny boy!
今天真不太平
It has not been a nice day!
兩輛摩托倒在卡車那兒
Two motors pulled over a truck,
剛好擋住了中間緝毒警的視線
Stumbled right in the middle of a narc stakeout.
十個全副武裝的哥倫比亞人就足以對付我們
You know, ten colombians and scorpios armed to fuck all.
他們想回老巢
They're trying to get in their headquarters.
我們得阻止他們
We're keeping them pinned down.
不過那些警察就快因出血過多而死了
but those officers are bleeding to death.
他們快不行了 警官
Fuck! they're dying, man.
他媽的重武器在哪兒
Where the hell is special weapons?
它們還在聖佩德羅和牙買加人交火
They're still tied up in that shootout in san pedro with the jamaicans.
他們擊落了一架直升機
They shot down a chopper.
米爾斯和詹森快頂不住了
Mills and Johnson won't last much longer.
我們需要一輛裝甲車去救他們
We need an assault vehicle to go get 'em.
好吧 我來想想辦法
I'm gonna chat with these assholes.
- 看我信號 給我火力掩護 - 明白
- When I give the signal, give me some cover! - Got it!
這也太小了
Too small.
就這樣吧
Right.
快點 快點
Come on! come on!
快帶他們離開這兒
Get 'em out of here! now!
來吧
Vamonos!
動作快點
Get 'em out! get 'em out!
- 來吧 - 來吧
- Vamonos! - Vamonos!
你們這些狗雜種
Hey, assholes!
邁克 你沒事吧
Mike, are you ok?
沒事 快去抓那些餘孽
yeah. let's get the rest.
不行 海納曼指揮官有命令
we can't. orders from chief heinemann.
讓我們原地待命
He says surround building and wait.
- 待什麼命 - 我怎麼知道
- Wait for what? - I don't know!
也許是特種部隊 聯邦探員 毒品管制局
Some bullshit special unit. the feds, the dea.
如果等那幫傢伙來插手
If we let those bastards get dug in now
我們得將這座房子夷為平地才能抓住他們
we'll have to level the building to get them out
- 狗娘養的 - 沒錯
- Hijo de puta. - No, es para mi.
來吧 行動吧
Vamonos!vamonos!
趕快來吧
Venga!aprisa!
來吧
Venga!
我們準備好了 來吧
Come and get it. ei scorpio is ready.
- 警官 上面有你們的人嗎 - 沒有
- Sarge, any of your people in the building? - No.
行動
Let's go.
中尉 你不能進去 海納曼馬上就到
Lieutenant, can't let you in. Heinemann's on his way.
讓他去死吧 動作快點
Heinemann can kiss my sweet ass! come on!
該死的 跟上他
Goddamn it. go with him.
三 二 一
Three, two, one...
行動
Go!
出去 退後
Get back, back, back. back.
隔壁也檢查完畢
Next door over.
在門口守著
Take this room!
我們在二樓 有人受傷 請求支援
First floor, officer down. we need backup.
別動
Freeze!
我說別動
I said hold it!
把槍放下
Now, lay your guns down.
是走下來還是跳下去隨你便
you can walk down or fly, it's your choice.
但先把槍放下 混蛋
I said put it down, asshole!
不
No!
過去看看
let's do it now!
放鬆
Take it easy.
真他媽熱
Damn, it's hot.
肯定是眼花了
Must be losing it.
邁克
Mike!
散開 搜查整個屋頂
Spread out. secure the roof.
沒事了 我在這
Just take it easy. I'm righthere.
警報解除 一切正常
All clear. all clear on the site.
丹尼
Oh, dannyboy.
我得下去了
I gotta get down from here.
天哪
Shit.
全面搜查 哪層都不要放過
Ok, search the roof. check every floor.
也許還有餘黨
maybe someone else...
把這裏封鎖起來 不許任何人離開
Seal it off. no one leaves.
丹尼 快讓我離開這鬼地方
Danny, get me off this damn roof.
- 找到他們的同黨了嗎 - 有人捷足先登了
- You get the rest of them? - Somebody beat us to it.
利昂娜
Leona.
我的天哪
Oh, shit.
這兒發生了什麼
what happened to ei scorpio?
他正在吃午餐
He's out front having lunch.
這究竟是怎麼回事
What the hell is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
他們都身首異處
They've been cut to pieces.
肯定是牙買加人
must be the jamaicans.
像他們的風格 但他們去哪兒了呢
their style, but where the hell did they go?
法醫來以前 不准任何人進這裏
Ok, nobody gets in here until forensic arrives. nobody.
你知道程序的
Ok, you know the drill.
邁克 你看上面
Mike. Up there.
他肯定是在這兒被殺 然後有人...
He must have been killed out here, and then someone...
起碼有35到40英尺高 沒有繩子和梯子
That's about 35, 40 feet. no rope, no ladder.
這傢伙有190到195磅
The guy weighs about 190, 195 pounds.
你肯定不能把他掛在那
You couldn't carry him up there.
中尉
Lieutenant?
副指揮官海納曼在樓下
Deputy chief heinemann's downstairs.
他要你和你的人趕快離開這兒
he wants you and your people out of the building now.
這個混蛋
Ah, son of a bitch.
到底發生了什麼事
What the fuck is going on?
這不是好兆頭 邁克 一點都不好
This is not good, mike. not good at all.
- 查查這傢伙的底細 - 我會的
- I want a real name on this joker, ok?  - You got it.
邁克
Mike.
菲爾 你怎麼也在這兒
Phil, this is quite a surprise.
什麼風把你吹來了
what brings you down from the palace?
邁克 你讓我很失望 我現在很不高興
You let me down, mike. you're making me look bad.
我以為我們已經達成共識
I thought we had an understanding.
我費盡心思讓你到這來
I put my ass on the line to get you here,...
只希望你能合作一點
..and all I expect is a little cooperation!
我告訴過你這是聯邦調查局的案子
You were told this was a federal matter.
你最好別插手 你竟然違抗命令
Yet you disobeyed an order to stay out of the building.
別這樣說 菲爾 是戰爭帶我來的
Don't let this get out, phil, but it's a fucking war down here.
當兵就要服從命令 別找借口
Soldiers take orders. don't push it!
菲爾 我沒有找借口
I'll push it as far as I can, phil
當你們在市區辦公室裏轉鉛筆的時候
cos we're fighting for our lives here,...
我們在這兒冒死戰鬥
..while you're downtown pushing pencils and kissing ass!
我不會聽任何人的 特別是聯邦調查局
I don't roll over for anybody, especially the feds,...
除非給我們一個好的解釋
..without a goddamn good explanation!
把這些儀器搬去三樓
Take this equipment up to the third floor.
開始行動
come on, let's move!
- 走吧 - 對不起 長官
- Let's go. - Excuse me, sir!
海納曼 他們到底在幹什麼
What the hell is going on here, heinemann?
不聽指揮
Insubordination.
不服從上級領導的命令
disregard for direct orders from a supervising officer.
滾回你阿瓦拉多的窩吧
Now get back to your cage at alvarado.
我讓你見識見識什麼是不聽指揮 你個...
I'll show you insubordination, you son of...
別
No, no, no!
你跑什麼 有種過來
Where you running to? come here!
沒必要這樣 邁克 何必呢
You don't need this, mike. it's not worth it.
放鬆一點
Relax.
真他媽的
Oh, fuck!
我為您帶來最新報道
I have an update for you.
這次交火 五名哥倫比亞毒販
In a shootout, five members of one colombian drug gang...
被他們的對手殺害
..were ambushed by their bloody rivals,
牙買加的伏都教徒神秘失蹤
the jamaican voodoo posse, who escaped withouta trace
再次愚弄了...
again making total fools of...
- 有位警官想見你 - 在那後面
- A detective is here to see you. - Back there.
聽著 女士 你家廁所漏水
Listen, lady, you got a backed-up toilet.
需要的是水管工而不是警察
Call a plumber, not the cops.
你的執照過期了
This licence has expired.
胡扯 我六個月前付過錢了
Bullshit! I paid that fee six months ago.
- 小心我揍你 - 坐下 趕快
- I'll kick your ass! - Sit down! right now!
- 走 快走 - 你他媽冷靜點
- Move! get your ass movin'! - Just calm the fuck down!
你在看什麼
What you lookin' at?
你要做的就是
And all you got to do...
把球放在球座上 然後揮桿
..is tee it high and let it fly.
完美的揮桿
Ow! dead solid perfect.
你要記住
Now, remember
你要看好距離 緊緊地抓住球桿
for distance you gotta gently but firmly grip the club.
哈里根中尉 我是探員蘭伯特 防衛司的
Lieutenant harrigan! detective lambert, rampart division.
小伙子 先坐一會 我一會找你
Hey, kid, just have a seat. I'll be right with you.
- 嘿 頭 - 你先別說 邁克
- Hey, cap. - Don't start, mike.
海納曼已經警告我
Heinemann's already been up my ass so
讓我小心我頭上的烏紗帽
Far I won't be able to sit down for a week.
我們贏不了他
We're not winning this war.
不管你願不願意 有些事你必須要做
As much as it'll piss you off, you'll have to play the game.
而且必須立即去做
"effective immediately,
聯邦特遣隊負責人彼得·凱斯
A federal task force under special agent peter keyes...
會調查一系列犯罪活動
Will investigate criminal activities
包括一些受限案件
Involving the trafficking of controlled substances."
你要全力配合他
And you will extend him your full cooperation.
你是要我把案子交給他嗎
So you're cutting off my dick and shoving it up my ass.
聯邦調查局是老大 我們得聽它的
The feds are calling the shots on this. my hands are tied!
什麼事
Peah?
皮爾格瑞姆上尉 我是彼得·凱斯
Captain pilgrim, peter keyes.
- 很高興見到你 - 我也是 長官
- It's good to meet you. - And you, sir.
邁克·哈里根中尉 聯邦調查局探員彼得·凱斯
Lieutenant mike harrigan. special agent peter keyes, dea.
久仰大名
Heard a lot about you.
很抱歉 這是司法程序
I'm sorry for this jurisdictional intrusion.
不是說我比你們權力大
Don't mean to be stepping on your toes.
我們只是想剷除金·威利的伏都教
But we want to prevent king willie's voodoo
他們控制了整個西海岸
Gangs from taking over the entire west coast.
我想多透露一些給你們
I wish I could tell you more.
但這牽涉到一些核心問題
But we have a large number of deep-cover operatives involved.
你們知道的 我們都有各自的職責
You know how it is. we all have a job to do.
現在 我保證
Now, I'm sure
我們會尊重彼此並各司其職
we can respect each other's situation and act responsibly.
合作是我突出的個性
Well,...um, cooperation...is my middle name.
一會見
I'll see you around.
我剛調過來 我叫吉瑞·蘭伯特
I'm the new transfer, jerry lambert.
聽我說 你先坐一會
Like I said, have a seat.
一會找你
I'll be right with you.
- 這個公子哥是誰 - 一個笨蛋
- Who is this dude? - Yeah, what an asshole.
丹尼 查到什麼了
All right, danny boy, what we got?
查到什麼?
What have we got?
裏面是五個來歷不明人
five lowlife scorpions make it into the building.
然後 他們變成了烤肉串
The next minute... they're all shish kebab.
沒有槍傷
Not one bullet wound.
不是為了毒品和錢 因為這些東西撒了一地
It wasn't drugs or money. there's a shit load of that.
也許金·威利雇了某個厲害角色
Maybe king willie brought in some outside talent.
他正顯示他的本事
He's making his big move.
他在我們上去之前已經解決了戰鬥
A pro would have split the moment he heard us.
不止殺了一個人 也許我們見到他了
More than one, we would have seen them.
究竟是誰在最後時刻
Whoever did this waited until the last minute,...
將四個手持機槍的
..and then took out four men
悍匪統統放倒
armed with machine guns by hand!
然後在我們眼皮底下溜走了呢
And then got by us.
也許我們應該僱傭他
let's put him on the payroll.Maybe we should give him a job.
當我和我搭檔守在樓梯上時
So me and my partner bolt up the stairs,
有人大叫血腥謀殺
Somebody is screaming bloody murder...
- 你聽我說 - 什麼
- You gotta... you gotta hear this. - What?!
嘿 忘了告訴你
Hey. hey, I forgot to tell you.
看見那傢伙了嗎
See that guy there?
他會接菲利斯的班
That's ferris's replacement.
他叫吉瑞·蘭伯特
This guy's jerry lambert.
是防衛司的獨行俠
the lone ranger from rampart station.
有他那樣的獨行俠嗎
That's the lone ranger?
我還以為他是來這兒修空調的
I thought he was here to fix the air conditioning.
我就說"女士你被捕了" 她說"為什麼"
I said "lady, you are under arrest." and she said "why?"
我說"因為你殺死了你丈夫"
I said "because your husband is dead. you killed him."
- 你知道她說什麼 - 不知道
- You know what she said, didn't miss a beat? - uh, no.
她說"我以前常常這麼刺這個混蛋
She said "i stabbed that son of a bitch plenty of times.
可他都沒死啊"
He never died on me before."
他好像在挑逗利昂娜
Looks like he's putting the moves to leona.
他犯的第一個大錯誤
His first big mistake.
我聽說過你
I have heard about you.
- 真的嗎 - 沒錯
- Yeah? - Yeah!
- 比如你上個搭檔被槍擊 - 什麼
- Like your last partner got shot. - What?
別老纏著我 笨蛋
You try that cowboy shit with me, fucker,...
要不然我把你閹了
..you can kiss these goodbye.
- 明白了嗎 - 明白了
- Got it? - Yeah, I got it. unhh!
我想你已經見過三位了
Well, well, I see that the three of you have met.
蘭伯特 如果你還忍得住
Lambert, if you're feeling up to it,...
可以慢慢地走到中尉那
..why don't you limp your way in to the lieutenant.
他想和你談談
He wants to talk to you.
好的
Yeah.
- 你真是個壞女孩 - 我喜歡這樣
- You're a bad girl. - Ooh, I like that.
不 不 不
No, no, no!
天哪 這女人是不是來月經了
Goddamn, is that bitch on the rag or what?
小伙子 接下來我所說的就是所謂的"規矩"
This is what I call "the speech", kid.
我只說一次 注意聽
I only give it once, so pay attention.
到目前為止 都是些小打小鬧的遊戲
Until now, it's all been fun and games, cops and robbers,
還有油炸圈
Dunking doughnuts.
但現在不一樣了 我得告訴你這是個戰區
But you're in the shit now. metro command is a war zone.
中尉 我明白
Lieutenant, I've paid my dues.
我費了很多功夫才調到這
I had to bust my ass to get my transfer.
這讓我很吃驚 小伙子
And that scares the shit out of me, kid.
沒人會要求到這來
No one requests to come here
除非他想揚名立萬
unless they want a reputation.
這裏沒有地方讓人表現自己
There's no room for anyone looking to prove themselves.
我也絕不允許這樣
I won't stand for it.
別讓我不高興
Don't get me wrong.
我們需要好警察
We need good cops
他們說你很棒
and they say you're good at what you do.
但是團隊精神是第一位的
But the team comes first.
以團隊為主 才是重要的
You live by that, and you'll be ok.
我們在等著你
and we'll all be there for you.
記住 凡事都有兩面
Remember, the door swings both ways.
就這些
That's it.
嘿 小伙子
Hey, kid.
歡迎加入戰鬥
Welcome to the war.
小子 是不是做的太過火了
Ok, guys. this has gone too far now, huh?
聽著 小子
Hey, hey, guys.
我知道你想恐嚇我
I-l-l know you're trying to scare me, huh?
你做的很好
Well, you did a pretty good job, man.
我現在很害怕
I'm scared now.
別這樣
Stop it now.
我給你錢
I can pay you.
兩百萬現鈔 馬上就給
$2 million, man. in cash. - - right now!
不是錢的問題
This is not about money.
是權利之爭
This is about power!
這裏會有新老大
There's a new king in the streets.
這是給你和你的手下提個醒
This is a message he has for your people.
你的時代過去了
You are history.
該死的歷史 普托
Fucking history, goddamn puto.
你他媽在幹什麼
What the fuck are you doing now, man?
你瘋了嗎
You're crazy!
金·威利說
King willie says...
我不僅能殺死你的肉體
..not only do I have to kill you,...
還能帶走你的靈魂
..but I have to take your soul.
伏都教的咒語
Voodoo magic.
該死的伏都教
Fucking voodoo magic, man.
但你知道嗎 我來告訴你我的信仰
But you know what? I tell you what I believe.
好戲上演
Shit happens.
快開槍
Shoot it!
混蛋
Fucker!
好戲上演
Sh... shit happens.
Shit happens.
我現在在聖佩德羅的別墅區外
I'm standing just outside a penthouse complex in san pedro...
有20人死亡
..involving as many as 20 people.
死者身份不明
it's uncertain who they were.
有報告指出
One report indicates
也許是恐怖的牙買加伏都教徒
It might be the feared jamaican voodoo posse.
我去做身體檢查 我的醫生說
I go in for my physical and the doctor says
"我需要精子 大便和尿樣"
"i need a semen,Stool and urine sample."
我說"醫生 我很忙
I say "gee, doc, I'm in a big hurry.
我能不能只把內褲留下"
can I just leave my underwear?"
上帝啊
Oh, god.
有消息稱
Word is
裏面至少有50具屍體
there may be as many as 50 more dead bodies up there.
看那 是波普
Oh, man, it's pope.
那個寄生蟲肯定住在車上
That parasite must live in his car.
我來處理 公共關係我最拿手了
I'll handle it. pr's my specialty.
他們說讓你別沾手這個案子
Word is they want your ass off the job.
- 托尼 夥計 - 你是誰
- tony, my man! - who the hell are you?
我是你最忠實的粉絲 每次都看你的演出
Your biggest fan! catch your show all the time.
- 我還有工作要做 - 你要做的就是滾遠點
- I got a job to do! - Your job is to root garbage for elsewhere.
進去過了?
Been inside?
是的 我們幾個當時正要進去
Yeah. we were gonna go in with our guys,...
但是接到無線電通知說
But we were told on a radio
不管發生什麼 任何人都不能進去
Transmission nobody goes in under any circumstances.
所有單位注意
All units, be advised.
聯邦調查員將接手調查
federal offcers will handle investigation.
- 我們什麼都沒聽到 走 - 你是老大
- we didn't hear that. let's go. - you're the boss.
謝麗爾·泰爾在現場為您報道...
This is cheryl tyer reporting live...
這手電筒真不錯 介意我借用一下嗎
Hey, nice flashlight. mind if I borrow it?
該死
Damn!
很眼熟
Look familiar?
操
Fuck.
老天
Oh, god.
雷蒙·維嘉 那個大毒梟
Ramon vega, the crack king.
是東洛杉磯最大的販子 每周賣出100公斤
Biggest operator in east LA. 100 kils a week.
為什麼他沒被剝皮 這些混蛋是什麼人
Why isn't he skinned? and who are they assholes?
是牙買加人
they are jamaicans.
金·威利的手下
King willie's boys.
這毫無意義
That makes no sense.
是伏都教儀式 我見過 他們挖出他的心
This was a voodoo ritual. I've seen it before. they took his heart out.
- 為了什麼 - 都是嚇人的方法
- what for? - Terror tactics, man.
為了把敵人嚇得屁滾尿流
You know, to scare the shit out of their enemies.
- 金·威利 - 誰是該死的金·威利
- king willie. - who the hell is king willie?
金·威利 伏都教洛杉磯分教的神父
King willie, voodoo priest of the LA posses.
在他的勢力變得強大前
Ran the terror gangs for Edward seaga in Jamaica...
幫愛德華·西嘉在牙買加運營恐怖組織
..till he got too powerful.
沒他允許 牙買加的頭頭們都不敢有所行動
The Jamaican chiefs won't make a move without his approval.
他媽的到底發生了什麼
So what the fuck happened?
該死!
Shit!
這裏有個倖存者
Hey, we got a survivor!
她在說什麼
What's she saying?
不知道 聽不清她在說什麼
I don't know. she's not making any sense.
她一直在說"惡魔來找他們了"
She keeps saying "ei diablo vino por ellos." the devil came for them.
如果這是那些哥倫比亞人幹的
If it's the colombians did this,
為什麼他們不管吊著的老大和裸體的女友
Why'd they leave their boss hanging and his girl naked on the floor?
這不是哥倫比亞人幹的
It wasn't the colombians.
難道是軍火庫的人?
Our friend from the armoury?
是的
Right.
我們有新的對手了
We got a new player in town.
過來 邁克 看看這個
Come over here, mike. check this out.
那是什麼
What is that?
看起來像矛頭或是什麼的
Looks like a spear tip or something.
這裏是禁區
This is a restricted area.
我希望你們馬上消失
I want it cleared immediately.
你正站在證據上面
You're walking on physical evidence.
- 我們來照顧她 - 我來 你們退後
- We'll take care of her. - She's with me.Just back off!
中尉 我想單獨跟你談談
Lieutenant, I'd like a word with you in private, please.
他們說堅持不懈是你最大的優點
They say that persistence is what your most outstanding quality.
- 我知道這事歸你管... - 你沒聽我說話
- I know this is your show... - you're not listening to me!
你太多管閒事 而且你干涉了太多我的工作
You got a big nose and you're sticking it too far in my business.
你聽好了 下次如果你再越界
Maybe you can hear this. the next time you cross me,...
你會永遠消失
you're gonna turn up missing.
蓋博 快把那個攝影師趕出去
Garber, the man with the camera.Get him.Right now!
是 長官
Yes, sir.
- 快點走開 - 站邊上點
- All right. Come on.let's go. - Stay away.
- 我操 把我的攝像機還給我 - 給我閉嘴
- Hey, fuck you, man! give me my camera! - Shut the fuck up.
等等 我有權在這兒 我是一名記者
Hey, wait a minute! I got my rights! I'm a journalist.
- 哈里根 - 閉嘴 快走
- harrigan! harrigan! - shut up. let's go.
你們想掩飾些什麼 媒體有權知道
Smells like a cover-up. the press has a right to know!
把他帶出大樓 搜他的身
Take him out of the building. search him.
你也給我滾出去
Now you get the hell out of here.
你是哪根蔥 凱斯
Who the hell are you, keyes?
是這個世界上你唯一不想惹的人
The last person in the world you wanna fuck with.
想讓我為你驕傲嗎 孩子
Wanna make me proud, kid?
盡你所能 跟住他們 查出他們帶她去哪兒
Take your bag of tricks, stay with them, find out where they take her.
稍後在洛杉磯賽塔酒吧見
Meet me later at la cita's.
小心 這些傢伙不好惹
And be careful. these guys are good.
不用擔心 監視是我的特長
Hey, don't worry! surveillance is my specialty.
很好 開始行動吧
Ok, then. just get going.
找到他們 獨行俠
Go get 'em, lone ranger.
丹尼 聽著 我們要好好處理這件事
Danny, look here. we gotta take this real cool.
這些傢伙雖然不是毒品管制局的人
These guys sure aren't the dea
但仍是凱斯的手下
But it's still keyes's party.
你呆在這兒 不要被發現了 我一點來見你
You stick around, stay out of sight. I'll meet you at one o'clock.
我們再好好搜查一下那房間 如何? 等我
We'll take a good look at that room, ok? hey, wait for me.
丹尼 不要逞英雄 明白嗎?
Danny boy, no hero stuff, understand?
丹丹 小丹尼
Dan-dan-dannyboy.
小心點 丹尼
Watch your ass, danny boy.
她沒有去醫院
She never made it.
聯邦調查員就在那等著
The feds were waiting.
直接把她載上了直升飛機
Hustled her off in a chopper.
我猜猜 那架銀色雲雀式直升機?
Let me guess. a silver alouette?
就是那架
That very one.
知道嗎 你的老朋友凱斯
And guess what. your pal keyes was running the whole show.
跟他的愚蠢的跟班 操縱著整個過程
And his butt boys.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
你做得非常出色 小伙子
You done real good, kid.
明天 開始跟蹤凱斯
Now tomorrow, start a tail on keyes.
注意他的一舉一動
Everything he does, every where he goes.
你會交上好運的
Who knows? you might just get lucky.
中尉
Lieutenant!
交好運
Luck...
...是我的特長
...is my specialty.
我深信不疑
Yeah. I bet it is.
不好意思 失陪一下 中尉
Now, if you'll excuse me, lieutenant,
我有一些重要的工作要做
I got some serious police work to attend to.
小妞我來了
Come to papa.
- 你的蛋蛋還好吧了? - 很好
- Hey, are your balls ok? - Fine.
你的呢
How are yours?
- 不好意思 她是我妹妹 - 什麼
- Hey, do you mind? it's my sister. - Say what?
其實你不是
Oh, you're not my sister,aren't you.
混蛋 你到底在找誰 凱斯
Son of a bitch. who are you really chasing, keyes?
該開工了
Time to go to work.
- 該死的 - 丹尼
- Shit.  - Dannyboy.
邁克
Mike?
老天
Oh, god!
不 不 上帝啊!
No. no. oh, god!
聖母瑪利亞
oh, mother of god!
求你別殺我
please, no!
...有暴力傾向 為強迫型人格
...violence prone, obsessive/compulsive personality,
慣用武力
...a history of excessive physical force...
...做了18年的洛杉磯警察
...throughout his 18 years as a los angeles police offcer.
對11輛警車和1輛公共汽車的損壞
Also responsible for the destruction
有著不可推卸的責任
of 11 patrol cars, a citybus...
那你又怎麼看他在警局期間
What about ten commendations for valour...
多達10次的嘉獎
What about ten commendations for valour
以及屢破重案的記錄
and the best felony arrest record in the history of this department?
因為我的干預
That and my intervention on your behalf
你才能保住你的烏紗帽
Are the only reasons you still have a job.
但是如果讓局長知道的話
If it were up to the chief,
他會就丹尼的死起訴你並停你的職
He'd charge you with detective archuleta's death and suspend you.
事實上 他把這件事交給了我處理
As it is, he left it in my hands.
現在 這種無視政策
Now,This John wayne attitude
一意孤行作風將不復存在
flagrant disregard for policy is gonna end now.
在我的指揮下
No one under my command will
沒有人能阻止這次由凱斯領導的
impede the progress of this federal task force
聯邦調查行動
headed by agent Keyes.
沒有人
No one.
就這樣
That's it.
散會
Dismissed.
邁克 你管得太多了 放手吧
Mike, you're too close to this. stay out of it.
這是警察的事 他們不能讓警察局撒手不管
It's a police matter. they can't keep the department out of it.
我們會找到殺害丹尼的人的
We'll find Danny's killer.
隊長 我和丹尼一起在街頭
Captain, Danny and I came up together.
巡邏了15年
15 years on the fucking street!
不管誰殺了丹尼 我都會讓他血債血償
Whoever killed him's gonna pay. I'm gonna finish it.
擠什麼呀
Hey, come on. what is this?
聽好了 混蛋
Listen, shithead.
我不管你要對那個混蛋怎麼樣
I don't give a fuck what you want with
因為現在這是我的私事
this asshole because now it's personal.
他死定了
And he's a dead man.
你現在的行為超出了你的權限 我警告你
What you're dealing with is over your head. I'm warning you...
你根本不知道你在幹什麼
You! you don't know what you're dealing with.
該是我警告你 別他媽擋著我的路
And I'm warning you. stay the fuck out of my way!
- 我來收拾他 - 不
- I'll take care of him. - No.
由他去
Let him go.
我們快得手了
We're too close.
誠如所說
Claiming as his
牙買加和哥倫比亞毒梟掌握著真相
turf controlled by the jamaican and colombian drug lords.
請繼續看我們接下來的報道
Watch as we continue our report.
洛杉磯已經唾手可得
LA is up for grabs,...
這座曾經美好的城市將落入那些
the spoils of our once fine city going to the ruthless scum...
肆意製造屠殺和流血事件的人渣手中
who can spread the most carnage and blood in our streets.
五個混蛋人渣和一名優秀的警察
five assorted trash and one good cop
警局中最優秀的一員
one of the best on our force.
誰將是下一個受害者 而市長又在哪兒
Who's next? where's the mayor?
他甚至根本就不在洛杉磯...
He's not even in the city...
忘了他吧 都結束了
Forget it. it's over.
邁克 該死
Mike, god damn it.
知道嗎 這不是你一個人的戰鬥
This ain't your personal little war, you know.
我也愛丹尼
I loved Danny, too.
你告訴我們只有團隊作戰才能存活
Hey, you told me the only way you survive is because you're a team.
凡事都有兩面 記得嗎
The door swings both ways. remember?
好吧 我們並肩作戰
All right. we'll do it together.
告訴我一些關於凱斯的情況
Come on. talk to me about keyes.
過去三天我們一直在跟蹤他
we've been on him for the last three days.
他們根本就沒有找毒販子
and they're not looking for drug dealers.
而是在全市區安裝那些奇怪的雷達探測器
Yeah. they've been setting up weird radar sensors all over downtown.
我用盡了一切辦法去跟著他們
I used my whole repertory to keep up with them!
我嘗試用探測器掃瞄他們 但是被他們察覺了
I had scanners on them, but they scrambled my shit up.
他們的設備太先進 我根本無法靠近
They had equipment I can't begin to touch.
今天早晨...
And then this morning...
我把他們跟丟了 - 我們把他們跟丟了
- l lost 'em. - We lost them.
- 在哪跟丟的? - 弗農街和工業街街口
- Lost where? - vernon and lndustry.
- 他們就像人間蒸發了一樣 - 在屠宰區?
-I mean they like fucking disappeared! - the slaughterhouse district?
是的 這大熱天 我是說 熱得能燒烤了
Yeah, and in this heat, whoo! I mean, bo and barbecue!
不管凱斯在找什麼 他已找到了 或即將找到
so whatever keyes is looking for, he's found it, or damn close to it.
利昂娜 我想見金·威利
Leona, I want to meet with king willie.
看來我和威利有著相同的麻煩
Willie and I seem to have the same problem.
- 而你 跟我一起走 - 邁克 這無法辦到
- In the meantime, you come with me. - Mike, it's impossible!
就這麼決定了
Just do it.
該死!
Fuck!
歐米加一號 這裏是控制中心
Omega 1. this is control.
這裏是歐米加一號
This is omega 1.
我們只有二十二分鐘安全作業時間
We only have 22 minutes on safe window of operation.
- 是 長官 - 最後一次檢查遙測裝置
- Yes, sir. - Verify that final telemetry check.
開始測試
Start your test now.
跟蹤掃瞄 三 二 一
Scan track three, two, one,
開始
Mark.
六號 紫外線的正常啟動
Number six, power up on the uv banks.
紫外線已經完成 準備好接受測試
We're complete on the lower uv banks. ready for testing.
第二步 檢查周圍的溫度變化
Second level, check for ambient temperature variations.
你有兩分鐘時間 現在開始
You got two minutes. now get going.
所有單位
To all units.
所有單位 你們有大約20分鐘時間完成任務
All units, you have approximately 20 minutes to finish your task.
- 收到 - 增加這個紫外線
- Roger. - Increase this uv.
上升到42%
Up 42 per cent.
你朋友死於利器刺入胸腔
Your friend died as the result of an intrusion in the chest cavity
這差點把他的心撕成兩半
..by an edged weapon that nearly cleaved the heart in two.
死亡是瞬間發生的
Death was instantaneous.
他全身的骨頭都被去掉了 我從未見過
He was boned like a fish. I've never seen anything like this.
請別碰任何東西
Please, do not touch anything.
醫生 其他那些受害者的情況怎麼樣
Doctor, what about the other victims?
有什麼別的發現嗎
Anything there?
聯邦調查組帶來了他們自己的法醫
The federal team brought in their own forensic examiners.
我是這個城市的驗屍員和首席病理學家
I am the medical examiner and the chief pathologist in the city,
但是他們就這麼把我完全拋棄了
and they've cut me out completely.
不管怎樣 你能看到他們收集到的證據吧
Anyway you can get a look at evidence the feds have collected?
- 我是說 他們肯定做過實驗 - 這很困難
- I mean, they must have run tests. - It won't be easy.
醫生
Doctor,
這是我從丹尼的手裏找到的
l pried this from danny's hands.
正是它把丹尼引上了屋頂
this is what took him into the rafters.
- 這個幾乎沒有重量 - 但它卻像鋼鐵一樣鋒利
- It has almost no weight. - But it cuts like steel.
讓我來看看
Let me see.
現在我們把它放大十五萬倍
We are now at 150,000 times normal magnification.
真令人驚訝
Astonishing.
這種元素根本不存在於元素週期表上
This material doesn't correspond to anything on the periodic table.
- 中尉 那到底是什麼 - 我不知道
- lieutenant, what the hell is that thing?  - I don't know.
但肯定不是五金店裏買的
It's not from a hardware store.
- 不是軍用的嗎 - 很好的假設
- No military?  - Uh, good guess.
不是他們丟的 就是他們想找的
Either something that got away, or something they want.
凱斯 我們已經離真相很近了
Keyes. ah, we're getting closer now to what happened
住手
Hey, no!
放鬆 小伙子 把你的搶收起來
Easy, kid. put your gun away.
金·威利要見你
King willie will see you now.
- 沒事 - 你不想我跟你一起去
- It's ok. - Don't you want me with you?
稍後我打給你
I'll call you later.
- 你想我跟著你嗎 - 稍後我打給你
- You want me to follow you? -I'll call you later!
整點大麻怎麼樣
You want some ganja, man?
車牌號
License plate number.
1- 8- 8
1-8-8
不不不 1- 8- 8- 3
No, no. 1-8-8-3
該死!
Oh, fuck!
去你的"凡事都有兩面"
The door swings both ways, my ass.
這事兒也有兩面
This door swings both ways.
謝謝載我一程
Thanks for the ride.
你們
You know,
實在該少抽點煙
you guys really ought to cut down.
他們說你想跟我聊聊
They say you want to talk to me.
他們還說你在暗中幫助我
They say you're offering me favours.
告訴我你這麼做的原因 死警察
Tell me why, babylon.
警察先生
Mr policeman.
- 我需要一些情報 - 情報?
-I want some information. - information.
關於那個殺手嗎
About the one that's doing all the killing?
他先殺了你的人
He killed your people.
現在又來殺我的
Now mine.
我想你應該知道他是誰
I think you know who he is.
我想要找到他
I want him.
我不知道他是誰
I don't know who he is.
但我知道他在哪
But I know where he is.
- 在另外一個世界 - 你在胡說些什麼
- The other side. - What are you talking about?
在靈界中
The spirit world, man.
看到嗎
You see,
總是這樣的
it's always the same.
該來的還是要來
There's no stopping what can't be stopped.
該死的還是要死
No killing what can't be killed.
別故弄玄虛了
Hey, make sense, man.
殺了你跟我的手下的那個東西
This thing that's killing your people and mine
來自另外一個世界
is from the other side.
我能感受到他的存在
I can feel him all around.
但除非他來找你
You can't see the eyes of the demon...
不然就無法用肉眼看到他
until him come calling.
這真是恐怖
This is dread, man.
非常恐怖
Truly dread.
這裏沒你的事了 警察先生
Nothing else for you here, policeman.
走吧
Time to go.
時刻做好準備
Prepare yourself.
"他的基地在聖山之上"
"his foundation lie in the holy mountain."
"西拉"
"selah."
這裏是托尼·普波在充滿恐懼的
This is tony pope live from la,
洛杉磯城為您直播
the city of fear.
那個變態的殺手還在繼續著他每天的屠殺
The psycho-vigilante killer continues his daily diet for murder.
高掛的屍體
Bodies strung out,
被剝皮的屍體 以及從屍體中挖出的心臟
bodies with the skins ripped off, the hearts torn from the cadavers.
而就在剛才 金·威利 那個毒梟
And just recently, king willie, the drug lord,...
那個萬惡的毒梟 在一條小巷的轉角被殺了
the vicious drug lord found in an alley just around the corner...
他的頭被砍了下來 而脊椎則被拆散了
with his head cut off and his spinal column torn from the body.
真是死有餘辜
A fitting demise to the prince of powder.
先是丹尼 接著是金·威利 而你恰好都在
First danny, then king willie. and you were right there!
他在耍你呢 你得小心點
He's playing with you, mike. you've gotta be careful.
好的 我們都要小心 凱斯那邊怎麼樣
Yeah. we all gotta be careful. what about keyes?
- 有新發現嗎 - 凱斯這有點棘手
- Anything there? - Definitely something slippery about keyes.
全名叫彼得·J·凱斯
Seems there's a peter j keyes.
獲得了是康奈爾大學的物理學博士學位
Phd physical sciences, cornell.
以優異的成績畢業並加入戰略防禦研究所
Hot out of college and into the strategic defense lnstitute.
兩年後被任命為空軍情報部門的上尉
Then two years later commissioned as a captain in air force lntelligence.
邁克 我們查不下去了 超過我們範圍了
Mike, this is a dead end. we're way out of our league!
聽著 我不管他有多大的來頭
Look, I don't care how big this is and who's involved.
他殺了丹尼 他必須付出代價
This guy killed danny and he's going to fall!
- 醫生那邊怎麼樣 - 我在這 中尉
- Now whatabout the good doctor? - Yeah, I'm here, lieutenant.
聯邦當局清除了所有證據
The federal authorities erased everything from the computer file
除了這個
except for this
別墅的木碎片的部分化驗結果
Part of a chemical test on a fragment of wood from the penthouse.
它含有微量的牛血
And it contained traces...
和大量的類固醇
..of cattle blood and heavy traces of steroids.
我認為殺死丹尼的兇手
I believe whoever killed detective
最近曾到過屠宰場
Had recently been in a slaughterhouse.
屠宰場 正是我第一次跟丟凱斯的地方
Slaughterhouse.That's where llostkeyes the first time!
恩 我們會在那找到他的
Yeah. that's where we'll find him.
坐地鐵過來 一小時後伯恩斯車站見
Take the metro. I'll pick you up at Burns station in an hour.
你沒看到凱斯的人 不代表他不在附近
Justbecause you don't see keyes's boys doesn't mean they're notaround.
乖乖的在車裏坐著
I just want you to stay in the car. ok?
你媽媽和我馬上來 坐好別亂跑
Your mom and I won't be very long. you sit still.
我們很快就回來
We'll be back in a few minutes.
明白了嗎
All right?
- 走吧 親愛的 - 恩
- Come on, honey. - Yes.
- 走哪邊 - 從這邊過去
- which way was it? - Down here.
受死吧 你這只癩皮狗
Take that, you scum-sucking dog.
要吃糖嗎
Want some candy?
布賴恩 布賴恩
Brian? brian!
- 你立刻給我回來 - 媽咪 我看到鬼了
- You come here right this minute! - Mommy, I saw a ghost.
要吃糖嗎 要吃糖嗎
Wantsome candy? wantsome candy?
安息吧
Rest.
要吃糖嗎
Wantsome candy?
丹尼的項鏈
Danny's necklace.
我討厭在繁忙時段坐地鐵
I hate the subway at rush hour.
這時段空位很難找 如果你有幸找到了
It's hard enough to find a seat, and if you do,
上面要麼是有尿的 要麼是有屎的
Someone's pissed in it or thrown up over it.
熱死我了
This damn heat is killing me, man.
嘿 我上電視了
Hey, it's me!
- 我很上鏡啊 - 臭美
- I look great! - Oh, shit.
沒有簽名 大叔
No autographs, pop.
- 看 那兒有兩個空位 - 別碰我
- Look. there's two seats right there. - Don't touch me!
滾開
Hey! get off!
麻煩事真多
This shit never ends.
- 你來吧 - 混蛋
- After you. - Asshole!
- 請讓開一下 警察辦事 - 別擋路
- Excuse me. police business. - Get out of my way!
嘿 寶貝 親我一下 來嘛
Hey, baby. besame mucho. come on!
你看上去挺有同情心的嘛
You look like a sympathetic dude.
我的兄弟最近要做點買賣
My, uh... partner here needs an operation .
但我們手頭有點緊 你明白我意思吧
But we're a little short of cash, if you know what I mean?
不需要那樣
No need for that.
恩 錢啊
Mm, money.
滾開
get the hell away from me!
不要逼我 我真的會開槍的
I know how to use this thing! don't make me use this thing!
我敢打賭我的槍比你的大
Bet mine's bigger than yours!
我來搞定他
I'll take that.
- 住手 警察 - 這次麻煩大了
- Hold it. police! - We're in trouble now.
- 所有人都不許動 - 警察 不許動
- Nobody move! - Alto, policia, no se muevan!
大家深呼吸 別緊張
Everybody take a deep breath, loosen your sphincters.
別逞一時之勇
We don't need any rush-hour rambos there.
把槍放下 混球
Tu tambien, motherfucking baby!
放下槍 然後坐下 坐下
Drop it and sit down! sientate!
媽的那是什麼
What the hell is that?
利昂娜 你還好吧
leona, you ok?
它在車廂裏 帶乘客們離開
This is it! he's in the train! get these people out of here!
吉瑞
Jerry!
發生什麼事
What's happening?
趴下 趴下
Get down! get down!
快離開
Get out of the way!
吉瑞
Jerry!
利昂娜
Leona!
利昂娜 帶他們走 走啊
Leona, get 'em out! go! go!
快
Now!
吉瑞
Jerry!
利昂娜 快走啊
Leona, do it!
快
Now!
我在這裏
Hey! over here!
對了 過來吧
Yeah, that's right. come and get it.
快點 走啊 走啊
Come on! move it! move it!
走快點 走
Let's go! vamos!
走
move it!
別慌 走就可以了 走 快走
Don't panic, just go! go! vamos!
天哪 你是什麼東西啊
Jesus christ. what the fuck are you?
等一下
Wait!
走啊 走啊 快點
Vamos!vamos! come on!
向前走啊 快 你們兩個 走啊
Keep walking! come on, you too! vamonos!
來啊 狗娘養的
Come on, motherfucker!
要吃糖嗎
Wantsome candy?
讓我們跳舞吧
Let's dance!
快讓開
Come on, get out of the way!
讓開
Get out of the way!
快 出來 出來
Come on, out! out! out!
快點 跑
Come on, move it!
去那邊 去有光的地方
That way! that way! towards the light! the light!
快 都出來
Come on! get out!
快點啊
Come on.
走
Vamos!
天哪
Oh, god.
吉瑞
Jerry.
上帝 怎麼又殺人了
God, not again.
快離開 別擋著
Ok, move your ass! move out the way!
發生了什麼事
Watch out! what's happening?
他媽的真是一場屠殺 中尉
It's a fucking slaughter, lieutenant.
天啊
Oh, god!
吉瑞
Hey, jerry!
利昂娜
Oh, leona! leona!
醒醒 利昂娜
Oh, please. leona... oh.
- 她怎樣了 - 還活著 但過度驚嚇
- how's she doing? - deep shock, but she's alive.
我聽到胎兒的心跳 她懷孕了
I hear foetal heart sounds. she's pregnant.
立刻送到洛杉磯醫治
Let's move. la county. stat!
讓開點
Stand back.
數三下 一 二 三 起
On three. one, two, three. load up.
讓開
Out of my way!
讓開 快走開
Move out the way! move it! move it!
等一下 讓我看看
Uh, wait a minute. let me see.
- 吉瑞在哪 - 我不知道
- Where's jerry? - I don't know.
我們找到了他的警章
We found his badge.
哪些人受傷了
Who got hit this time?
五個小混混
Five gang members,...
一些乘客
..bunch of commuters.
這說不通啊
Doesn't make sense.
他們都有帶槍
They were all armed.
- 什麼意思 - 指揮官的電話
- What do you mean? - It's the chief.
在這等著 喂
Wait here. yeah?
- 那邊情況怎麼了 - 他媽的很糟
- What the hell's going on down there? - It's a damn nightmare.
這次遇害的都是平民
Civilians this time.
- 全都死了嗎 - 是 和之前的一樣
- Allkilled? - Yeah. just like the others.
媽的
Damn!
吉瑞
Jerry!
活見鬼 他媽的發生了什麼事
Holy shit! what the hell is going on here?
夥計 打開攝像機 快開攝像機
Hey, guys, get the camera on! get the camera on this right now!
拍下這些事
Get that goddamn thing on film!
發生了什麼事
What's going on?
哈里根
Hey, harrigan!
這次受害人更多 損毀更嚴重
More victims! more mutilations!
- 去死吧 - 普波
- Fuck you! - Pope!
普波 你還在嗎 普波 發生了什麼事
Pope? are you there, pope? pope, what's going on?
長官 那個警察又來了
Sir, the cop is back.
媽的
Goddamn.
哈里根 你就不能省點兒力氣嗎
Harrigan! don't you show up in the damnedest places.
過來 中尉 我有些你會感興趣的東西
Come here, lieutenant. I got something you might find interesting.
這裏是怎麼回事
What is this?
我要跟你說多少遍
How many times do I have to tell you?
你不知道你的對手是什麼
You don't know what you're dealing with.
這個就是你要找的兇手 很妙吧
There's your killer. wonderful, isn't it?
他的身軀散發出信息素 即氣味分子
Pheromone signature left by his body. scent molecules.
打開三號監視器
Punch up three.
十年前 一隻同種類的異形在中美洲
Ten years ago one of his kind eliminated an
摧毀了一支特種精英部隊
Elite special forces crew in central america.
只有兩個倖存者
There were two survivors.
他們說 這種生物一旦被捕
They indicated that, when trapped,
就會啟動一種自毀程式
The creature activated a self-destruct device...
威力足以摧毀三百個街區那麼大的雨林
..that destroyed enough rainforest to cover 300 city blocks.
完美的武器
Remarkable weaponry.
沒錯 中尉 他是外星生物
That's right, lieutenant. other-world life forms.
什麼
Huh?
一隻他媽的異形
A fucking alien!
硫磺島 柬埔寨 貝魯特
Iwo jima, cambodia, beirut.
發出熱能和引起矛盾
Drawn by heat and conflict.
他在進行著狩獵遊戲 獅子 老虎 熊
He's on safari. lions. the tigers. the bears.
我的天
Oh, my!
獎品 那是一場遊戲 對吧 凱斯
Trophies. that's the game, isn't it, keyes?
你就是獅子
You're the lion.
這裏是它的叢林
This is his jungle.
- 那為什麼我們看不到它
- So why can't we see him?
因為它有超強的自衛適應系統
defensive adaptations are astounding.
它能彎曲光線 完美的偽裝術
It's somehow able to bend light. perfect camouflage.
- 你欣賞這隻怪物 - 不是它的所作所為
- you admire the son of a bitch. - not what he does.
而是它本身的構造
For what he is.
還有它能帶給我們的東西
For what he can give us.
這將會是科技的一個新時代
A new era of scientific technology.
我一生都在等這機會 我不會讓它白白溜走
I've waited a lifetime for this, and I'm not going to miss the chance.
信息素雷達掃瞄儀發現它了
We have something on the pheromone scanners.
目標在屋頂上
Target one is on the roof.
我們花了兩周的時間摸清了它的習慣
- it's taken us two weeks to learn his patterns.
它每隔兩天就來這裏開餐一次
He comes here every two days to feed.
- 看來它很喜歡牛肉 - 我沒覺得是素食者
- seems he has a taste for beef. - I didn't think he was vegetarian.
我們為這只食肉獸準備了一個陷阱
Well, we've prepared a trap for this predator.
我們肯定這種生物
We are certain that this being can see in
只能用紅外線看物體
only one spectrum of light infrared.
紅外線?
Infrared?
它靠感應熱量捕食
He hunts by seeing our heat.
隔絕了熱量 它就是瞎子
Block the heat and he's blind.
這衣服能隔絕身體的熱量 使它看不到我們
These suits insulate body heat, making the team invisible to the creature.
我們在地面上覆蓋了一層放射性粉末
We've flooded the place with radioactive dust...
並在每一個角落都安裝上強紫外光燈
..and installed powerful ultraviolet lighting everywhere.
這種粉末粘附在它身上就會使它現形
The dust adheres to his body, making him visible.
液氮 你們不是要殺它而是要冰凍它
Liquid nitrogen. you're not gonna kill him. you're gonna freeze him.
- 我們要生擒它 - 它在移動了
- We have to capture him. - He's moving.
終於來了
Finally.
找個位子 好好看表演吧
Grab a seat. enjoy the show.
這是歷史性的時刻
This is history.
我們的目標是生擒並隔離它
Capture and isolation is our objective.
只有在我下令的時候才能防衛
Defensive action only on my orders.
開燈 行動
Power up. lights on. let's get him!
我們已經進入
We're in.
切換到紫外線
Switch to ultraviolet.
-  停止通話 - 打開A到J區的紫外線燈
- Radio silence. out. - engage ultraviolet units a through j.
- 這些干擾信號是什麼 - 正在調整 長官
- What's all this interference? - Correcting the problem, sir.
他們正在走向二區
They're moving to the second level.
目標仍在朝二號樓梯井移動
Target's still moving, heading towards the number two stairwell.
它正在往陷阱裏鑽
Playing right into it.
等一下
Wait a minute.
它停住了
It's stopped.
它退到牆邊了
It's moving back against the wall.
它正往回走 離他們越來越遠了
It's backing up. it's moving away from them.
你的人被耍了
Your boys have been made.
長官 它現在在他們周圍兜圈
Sir, it's circling around behind them.
讓他們出來 他們掉進陷阱裏了
Get 'em out! they're walking into a trap!
凱斯 它在三樓 就在你們後面
Keyes, he's behind you. third floor structure. right there!
誰在那裏囉嗦 不准通訊
Who is this? clear the line.
它看得見那該死的光 把他們關掉 關掉
He sees the damn lights. turn 'em off! turn 'em off! shit!
制止他
Stop him!
- 把門打開 - 你去死吧
- Door. open it. - Go fuck yourself.
好啊 好
Ok. ok.
開門
The door.
- 好的 我開 - 你知道你在做什麼嗎
- Yes, sir. - You don't know what you're doing.
開了
It's open.
- 你會把所有東西搞砸的 - 去死吧
- You'll ruin everything!  - Fuck yourself!
防衛隊形一 液氮槍關閉
Defensive formation one. nitrogen guns, safeties off.
大家跟著我
Everyone else, follow me .
它就在這裏
This is it.
它正向你們移動 右邊
He's moving down to your position, right.
蓋博 它在哪兒 我看不到它
Garber, where is he? I can't see him.
它就在那裏 它就在那裏
He's right there! he's right there!
媽的 它在哪兒 告訴我它的坐標
Goddamn it! where is he? well, give me a coordinate! where is he?
- 小心 - 天哪
- Watch out! - My god.
小心你的槍
Watch your crossfire!
媽的
damn
我的防護衣漏氣了
I'm losing my pressure.
凱斯 你怎樣了
Keyes, you all right?
凱斯 它在這裏
Keyes, it's overhere!
快 媽的
Come on! damn it.push over!
媽的 我什麼都看不到
Shit! I can't see!
通訊都中斷了
They're gone.
他們全死了
They're all dead.
你想殺我嗎 我就在這兒
You want me? here lam!
你真是一隻
You are one...
醜陋的
..ugly mother...
混蛋
Motherfucker!
猜猜誰回來啦
Guess who's back.
你回不了家啦
Too late to go home now.
快離開這裏 哈里根 我來救你
Get out of here, harrigan. I'm gonna save your ass.
這是我和他之間的戰鬥
This is between me and him!
天哪...
God...
原來是鳥
Birds.
該死的鳥
Damn birds.
好吧 膿包臉
Ok, pussyface
動手吧
It's your move.
好戲上演
Shit happens.
啊 天哪
Oh, god. oh, god.
我現在需要像鳥一樣
That's all I need is birds.
你行的
You can do it.
我可以做到的 我行的
I can do it. I can do it.
就像從樹上滑下來那樣
It's like falling off a log.
媽的 三十層樓高的樹
Like a 30-storey log. damn!
我可能會很好運地到達
Maybe I'll get lucky and fall.
媽的
Damn it.
伯倫加利亞 在賽普洛斯嫁給國王以後
..berengaria, who never set foot in england, was its queen for eightyears...
當了八十年的皇后 卻從未踏足英國
..aftermarrying this king on cyprus.
晚安
goodluck.
赫伯 赫伯 醒醒
Herb? Herb, wake up!
有人在我們家浴室
There's somebody in the bathroom.
赫伯
Herb!
- 別怕 我是警察 - 我不認為它怕你
- It's all right. I'm a cop. - I don't think he gives a shit.
媽的
Shit!
快回屋裏去
Get back inside!
媽的 又要往下滑
Holy moses. not again. shit!
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
上帝啊
Oh, god.
為什麼這隻怪物不呆在地面上啊
Why can't this guy stay on the ground?
過來 過來
Come on, come on. come on, come on!
過來這裏
Come to papa.
停 把電梯停住
Stop! stop the elevator!
停啊
Stop it!
這是什麼鬼地方啊
Now where the hell am l?
你在哪
Where are you?
上帝啊
Jesus christ.
這就對了 混蛋
That's right, asshole!
好戲上演
Shit happens!
好 誰接著來
Ok. who's next?
拿去
Take... it.
1715年
"1715."
哈里根 那裏他媽的發生了什麼事
Harrigan! what the fuck happened in there, huh?
活見鬼 我們差點就成功了
Goddamn it. we came so close!
別擔心 混球 你還會有機會的
Don't worry, asshole. you'll get another chance.